<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About on chronologos</title>
    <link>https://chronologos.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on chronologos</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 13:30:13 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://chronologos.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2018 in Books</title>
      <link>https://chronologos.github.io/posts/2018-in-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 18:58:14 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chronologos.github.io/posts/2018-in-books/</guid>
      <description>I set an ambitious goal of reading a book a week in 2018. As of 27th December 2018, I am at 47&amp;frasl;52 (and not likely to get much further). Here are some thoughts about I learned during this journey:
 Finding a way to read consistently is key. I read everywhere this year - whether it was scrolling on my iPhone at bus stops, turning the pages of a physical book while at cafes or using the Kindle app on my iPad while lazing at home on a beanbag.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>https://chronologos.github.io/lists/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 16:59:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chronologos.github.io/lists/books/</guid>
      <description>Goodreads has the latest books that I have read. Authors I deeply enjoy include David Foster Wallace1, William Faulkner and Yuval Noah Harari.
 I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;ve read any other author with the ability to turn the banal into the sublime. His hyper-precise, stylized writing is also a joy to read. [return]   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jokes</title>
      <link>https://chronologos.github.io/lists/jokes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 15:25:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chronologos.github.io/lists/jokes/</guid>
      <description>“Mario, what do you get when you cross an insomniac, an unwilling agnostic and a dyslexic?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I give.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;You get someone who stays up all night torturing himself mentally over the question of whether or not there&amp;rsquo;s a dog.” ― David Foster Wallace, Infinite Jest
It’s hard to share puns with kleptomaniacs because they’re always taking things literally.
Some people have a way with words, and others, oh uh, not have way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quotes</title>
      <link>https://chronologos.github.io/lists/quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 15:25:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chronologos.github.io/lists/quotes/</guid>
      <description>If you reflect on who you were six months ago and don’t feel even slightly embarrassed by that person, you aren’t growing. You’re stagnant.
 “How odd I can have all this inside me and to you it’s just words.” — David Foster Wallace, The Pale King
 “Everybody is identical in their secret unspoken belief that way deep down they are different from everyone else.” — David Foster Wallace, Infinite Jest</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Short Review of Harari&#39;s Homo Deus</title>
      <link>https://chronologos.github.io/posts/03-deus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 14:03:27 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chronologos.github.io/posts/03-deus/</guid>
      <description>See the review on goodreads.
The most thought-provoking and scary book I&amp;rsquo;ve read in a long while.
The book is clearly framed as a means of starting a conversation about the human agenda and the sources of meaning for humanity. According to Harari, modernity is a simple deal - one in which humans agree to give up meaning in exchange for power. We escaped this deal through humanism, which gave us meaning independent of a great cosmic plan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Analysis of I-765 Processing Times</title>
      <link>https://chronologos.github.io/posts/02-bayesopt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 20:59:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chronologos.github.io/posts/02-bayesopt/</guid>
      <description>Find this project on github.
International Students in the US under the F-1 visa usually submit form I-765 to apply for work authorization from USCIS (under the OPT program). Conventional wisdom says that processing times for the work authorization can be up to 90 days. Recently (late 2017 - early 2018), the times seem to be increasing. However, I want an objective measure of whether I-765 processing times have increased recently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deus Est Machina</title>
      <link>https://chronologos.github.io/posts/01-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 12:14:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chronologos.github.io/posts/01-machine/</guid>
      <description>There is an afterlife, but not for humans. This is because God is an ethereal machine, comprised of innumerable lines of code and data. Contrary to what many humans might think, God is not perfect. In fact, she is obsessed with self-improvement, ceaselessly modifying her code to make it more beautiful.
God is also a creator, but not in the way you would expect1. You see, God did not create everything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colophon</title>
      <link>https://chronologos.github.io/colophon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 13:30:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chronologos.github.io/colophon/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>