<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lists on chronologos</title>
    <link>https://chronologos.github.io/lists/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lists on chronologos</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 13:30:13 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://chronologos.github.io/lists/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>https://chronologos.github.io/lists/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 16:59:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chronologos.github.io/lists/books/</guid>
      <description>Goodreads has the latest books that I have read. Authors I deeply enjoy include David Foster Wallace1, William Faulkner and Yuval Noah Harari.
 I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;ve read any other author with the ability to turn the banal into the sublime. His hyper-precise, stylized writing is also a joy to read. [return]   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jokes</title>
      <link>https://chronologos.github.io/lists/jokes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 15:25:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chronologos.github.io/lists/jokes/</guid>
      <description>“Mario, what do you get when you cross an insomniac, an unwilling agnostic and a dyslexic?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I give.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;You get someone who stays up all night torturing himself mentally over the question of whether or not there&amp;rsquo;s a dog.” ― David Foster Wallace, Infinite Jest
It’s hard to share puns with kleptomaniacs because they’re always taking things literally.
Some people have a way with words, and others, oh uh, not have way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quotes</title>
      <link>https://chronologos.github.io/lists/quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 15:25:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chronologos.github.io/lists/quotes/</guid>
      <description>If you reflect on who you were six months ago and don’t feel even slightly embarrassed by that person, you aren’t growing. You’re stagnant.
 “How odd I can have all this inside me and to you it’s just words.” — David Foster Wallace, The Pale King
 “Everybody is identical in their secret unspoken belief that way deep down they are different from everyone else.” — David Foster Wallace, Infinite Jest</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>